CONTACT

- 9961699106
- ajithpg2411@gmail.com
- www.linkedin.com/in/ajith-pg
- ajithpq.github.io/my_portfolio
- Kerala.India

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Engineering, Computer Science APJ Abdul Kalam Technological university 2015 - 2019

SKILLS

JS Framework:

React JS, Next JS

Web Technologies :

HTML, CSS, Javascript, Jquery

CSS Framework

SASS, Tailwind CSS, Material UI

Tools

Git Version Control
VS Code Editor
UFT Automation

Design Tools

Figma

Adobe XD

AJITH PG

Front End Developer

ABOUT ME

Passionate Front-end web developer with 3+ years of experience in Web Developemnt uisng React, JavaScript, Jquery, HTML5, and CSS to build all aspects of the user experience and user interface for Websites, CMS Sites and e-commerce sites.

WORK EXPERIENCE

O Jan 2021- Present Tata Consultancy Services(TCS)

Front End Developer

- Implementing new client Requirements for Bank Trading Application
- Developing UI related Changes for the Application using Javascript

June 2020 - April 2021 GL InfoTech,Thrissur

React UI Developer

- Implemented new features and User interfaces in collaboration with clients and project team.
- Converting UI Design from scratch for Ecommerce and CMS Sites using React, HTML, CSS, SASS, Javascript
- Resolved browsers compatibility issues, Improving Website performance and SEO Rankings.

Dec 2019 - May 2020 i-Techtonic System,Coimbatore

Web Developer

- Design and Develop user interface for Websites
- Built web pages that are more user-interactive using Javascript,jQuery and Bootstrap.